Noah!
It's just like Leviathan!
So there were others?
You have your own will,
too, don't you?
In that case...
Obey me!
Fire
Water
Are you all right?
You tamed it?
Yes.
What? So quickly?
I should have known.
What brilliant judgment.
You chose Luthier without
the slightest hesitation.
Luthier...
It seems to possess a
great deal of power.
Would you like to test it?
I will prepare a target.
No, that won't be necessary.
Oh? Your eyes tell me you
have some sort of plan.
Now, here I go.
Noah...
It's all right.
Just as I predicted.
Leviathan is just slightly more powerful.
It doesn't feel hot...
Look at the ground.
Leviathan is keeping it in check
to prevent the heat from escaping.
You've tamed it to that point
already? Astounding...
I formally entrust Luthier to you, Noah.
Use it for the good of the empire.
I shall.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
The Meeres Empire holds dominion
over a vast amount of land.
Its highest ruler, the emperor,
governs all of its affairs.
This includes domestic affairs,
such as law and finance,
and diplomatic affairs, such as mediating
disputes and international negotiations.
The emperor also mediates in the
imperial family's private matters,
known as internal law
and internal affairs.
A personal declaration from the emperor's
younger brother, Graeme Ararat?
Graeme's son... my nephew.
He ruled over his domain
with extreme tyranny,
and now, in a drunken stupor,
killed someone during an argument.
That alone is a serious crime,
but his father, Graeme, has declared
a lack of oversight on his part
and personally offered to pay a fine.
Unfortunately, under imperial law,
Prince Graeme has committed no crime.
Just as a child is not responsible
for paying his parents' debts,
a parent is not responsible
for his child's crimes.
I said as much.
I suppose he's hoping
to buy peace of mind.
Thirty thousand rean...
That's about 250 times the average
yearly income in the capital.
It's a significant sum.
What do you think, Noah?
We cannot collect a fine from someone
who has committed no crime.
Even if he has offered to pay it himself.
Then shall we revise the law
to institutionalize voluntary
payment of fines?
The national treasury is
in chronic dire straits.
Disaster relief and suppression
of revolts do cost money.
So that's why he's hoping to bring
in incidental income like this.
I can't blame him, but...
If we were to set such a precedent,
people would get the idea that they can
get out of any crime just by paying money.
That would make the prevention
of crime more difficult.
And since only the wealthy
would be able to afford the fines—
major merchants, nobles, and
government officials—
it would eventually breed
corruption in our government.
The empire's lack of funds
is a grave problem,
but it is one we should resolve
through respectable means.
True. You were right to admonish me.
To celebrate your wisdom, the likes
of which we rarely see in a ruler,
I hereby name you my premier advisor.
Advisor?
It's an honorary post.
You dislike it?
Your Majesty, I have a proposal.
Why not allow people to pay money
not to escape punishment,
but to attain honor?
For example, those who donate
a thousand rean to the empire
may be granted honorary knighthood.
It will need caveats to ensure it
can't be abused to gain real power,
but many would love to be granted such
an honor by Your Majesty personally.
When humans...
come into possession of more
money than they can use,
they begin to desire honor more
than physical possessions.
I see. What a brilliant idea.
You impress me, Noah.
Cruz, summon Oscar. At once.
Of course.
Your Majesty.
I've just remembered some unfinished
business at the Ministry of Law.
Please allow me to take my leave.
This needs to stop.
If it goes any further, I'll be
intruding on Oscar's dominion.
You are clever, Noah.
They are all astonished by the
amazing feat you've performed.
Oh, it's you, Sheezu.
They can't comprehend how the ground
could simply melt away like that.
Someone has fallen into
it trying to find out.
How careless.
Here.
To treat the one who fell.
Spare no expense.
Thank you, Your Highness.
And this?
Ah.
Something I had delivered
for the Sixteenth Prince.
He is only three,
and he likes to make
rhinoceros beetles fight.
Huh...
Making them fight, eh?
Are you up to it?
Leviathan. Luthier.
They really do have
all the techniques of their
past owners engraved in them.
I'm learning a lot watching them, but...
The difference in strength is clear.
Wow!
Oh! Please pardon my intrusion!
That was magic, wasn't it?
Want to see it again?
May I?!
They seem up for it.
Unlike my faithful Leviathan,
Luthier seems quite competitive.
Learning their moves like this
might make me stronger, too.
Name: Minister-Prince of Justice Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 2
/
∞
My level went up!
Could it be...
Leviathan has won every
battle so far, but now...
Well done. You've come into your own.
Fire
Water
Wind
Earth
With Luthier's growth, the plus
on my fire stat has gone up.
And...
Zoey.
Understood.
By the power of the spirits with
whom I have forged a pact,
In the six years since I hired her,
tell me this individual's
intentions and disposition.
Zoey has learned many skills to repay
the debt she feels she owes me.
It went up.
Level
Amazing! You didn't even
have to do any fighting!
I've never heard of anything like this!
This is the result of
making my dolls battle.
S-So if you keep making them fight,
will it keep going up forever?
It isn't that simple.
To raise it from Level 1 to 2
took only one battle,
but to raise it from 2 to 3, I had
to make them fight over ten times.
I think fighting the same opponent
every time is inefficient.
Ah, I see.
If I want to learn how it
works in better detail,
I'll need to collect even
more magic items like these.
Now that sounds interesting.
Henry Ararat
Minister-Prince of Military Affairs, Fourth Prince
Brother.
Making your magic sword battle your ring?
That's the inventiveness I expect of you.
Where were you watching from?
The monster nest has finally matured.
It's time for your first campaign.
The monster nest...
A hunting ground managed by the
Ministry of Military Affairs
for the purpose of serving as
every prince's first campaign.
When you open this box,
it'll give a reading of how many soldiers
you should take on your first campaign.
We have a system for that?
You don't want too many or too
few for this sort of thing.
Go on, open it.
One?
Does that mean I alone am sufficient?
I don't believe it...
This is unprecedented.
You really are amazing, you know that?
Pardon me.
You have a visitor.
He says he brings orders
from His Majesty.
Let him in.
Reiss Keiki
Direct Subordinate of the Fourth Prince
Emperor's orders.
Yes, sir.
Someone who delivers a personal order
from the emperor can be
considered his proxy.
He must be shown the same courtesy
as the emperor in every aspect.
Wise Prince Noah Ararat's first
campaign will be postponed.
Stand by until you
receive further orders.
Understood.
It is good to see you
again, Your Highness.
Oh, right. Reiss. You are
part of Henry's household.
I am.
Members of the imperial family
sometimes send one of their slaves or
servants away to serve as officials.
Those of such origins are considered
members of that noble's family who have
been discharged from their service.
They are considered government officials
and subordinates of the imperial family.
Noah
Henry
Imperial Family
Household
Member
Subordinate
Reiss
The imperial household members who
work in service to each prince
have the strictest etiquette
standards imposed on them.
Why has it been postponed?
Entirely because of your strength.
The emperor was so delighted
by the unprecedented reading,
he said it should be
carried out on a grand scale.
So that explains it.
His Majesty is currently working with
Prince Henry and the Eighth Prince
to come up with a way to share how
remarkable you are with the whole empire.
Then I guess my first campaign
won't happen for a while.
Magic items that possess their own will?
Yes.
Anything will suffice.
Something like a cursed doll,
for example.
I'm terribly sorry.
I don't have anything like that.
I see.
Well, I didn't expect to
find more right away.
Shirley, if you please.
R-Right.
Take this.
If you come across anything that
might fit the bill, contact me.
B-But... I can't accept that!
Oh, and of course, I'll reward you
again if you find anything good.
I'm counting on you.
Th-Thank you so much!
What is it?
I'm very sorry.
I just can't believe you paid him so
much when he didn't have anything.
That's how nobles shop.
Do you even know who I am?!
Say that again if you think you can!
What did you say?!
I said that another customer has
already reserved that item...
And I'm telling you that I'll buy it!
Hey, what's with those looks?
You guys all do business
here too, don't you?
You want to lose your deals with us?!
Stop.
Huh?! Who the hell are—
Well, if it isn't Prince Noah!
You know me?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am a member of
Prince Gilbert's household.
My name is Dalem.
I once saw you at the Ministry
of the Imperial Household.
And why is a man like you doing this?
That was intimidation.
What's this now?
You are the minister-prince of
justice, and you don't know?
Those in the Ministry of the Imperial
Household can't be found guilty
of any crimes other than insurrection
or assisting an enemy.
I am quite familiar with
imperial law myself.
So I would rather you
didn't say anything to me,
no matter how trifling it may be.
Prince Noah?
Servants of the imperial family,
especially princes,
already enjoy quite high status.
And he's a member of the
First Prince's household
and the Ministry of the
Imperial Household.
He's privileged enough that his
attitude isn't surprising.
I understand clearly.
But...
But? But what?
You said you are a member
of my brother's household.
If so, why are you standing up
straight when you look at me?
It's the same as when
I saw Reiss yesterday.
Based on our positions, Dalem
should be showing respect to me.
I-I didn't realize—
Too late. Apprehend him, Shirley!
Right away!
But I am Prince Gilbert's...
Silence.
You still don't understand that
you've tarnished my brother's name?
Dalem, part of the First
Prince's household,
has behaved rudely toward
the Thirteenth Prince.
He will be punished under internal law.
Who has a whip?
I do!
Why are you people just watching?!
You'll regret this, damn it!
I swear you will!
I'll make sure you pay!
I am of the Ministry of
the Imperial Household!
How many lashes?
Well, let's see...
If you or one of my household
tyrannized my people under the
mantle of borrowed authority,
I wouldn't hesitate to
sentence you to death.
Understood.
Y-Your Highness! Please forgive me!
Serves you right!
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
All you ever did was throw your
weight around to screw us over!
Your Highness!
He has breathed his last.
All right. Has law enforcement arrived?
Yes.
Once all is taken care of,
have them write a report
with the charges I described earlier.
Understood.
Also, get me a set of handcuffs.
Huh?
Oh, if it isn't the Thirteenth Prince...
I've come to apologize to my brother.
Would you tell him that, please?
Let him in.
Who is that man?
His butler, Coil.
Please enter. Prince Gilbert awaits.
Episode 8
The First Versus the Thirteenth
I see. Well, there was no
other way to handle it.
A mere member of my household dared
to disparage an imperial prince.
Gilbert Ararat
First Prince
He deserved death.
Still, I should have
consulted with you first.
I sincerely apologize.
But... Dalem... Dalem, you say?
I don't remember that name.
If I may...
He relocated to the Ministry of the
Imperial Household a few years ago.
Oh, right, him.
All the more reason not
to fret over this.
I fired him and sent him
away for misconduct.
He couldn't even be called
a member of my household.
I see. So that's it.
In fact, I would even go so far as
to say you protected my reputation.
Had he been left to his
own devices any longer,
he would have continued to carry
out evil deeds in my name.
Thank you, dear brother.
But I can see why His Majesty
named you the keeper of the law.
Most wouldn't have carried out his
sentence on the spot like that.
Um, Prince Noah...
What was the purpose of that apology?
Hmm?
Well, you see...
You're asking if it was necessary
to go see him in handcuffs
when he seemed so nonchalant
about the whole thing?
Oh... Yes, exactly!
Despite how he looked, he was furious.
But he couldn't afford to create
a rift between him and me.
The emperor favors me more than
him right now, after all.
Oh...
If the younger brother apologizes
first after doing something wrong,
what does the older brother do?
Oh, that I can understand!
He can't get mad if the younger
brother apologizes first.
Not to mention my brother disavowed Dalem
and the slave traders with such ease.
If I'd done nothing, I'd become
a target for harassment.
Behind the curtain,
he sees me as an enemy.
I apologized, and he accepted it.
Among nobles, rehashing a problem
previously apologized for is unseemly.
You gave it that much thought?
Incredible!
Prince Noah, you have a visitor.
You're the one showing
them in? How unusual.
He says he's from the Ministry
of the Imperial Household.
All right.
It's an honor to meet you.
My name is Don Orts.
What do you want?
I was deeply impressed by how you
handled yesterday's incident.
I have come to ask that you allow
me to work under you as well.
Me? But our jurisdictions are different.
A member of the Ministry of the Imperial
Household would struggle here.
I don't mind.
You can simply use me
whenever you have the need.
Very well.
Thank you!
Dylan.
Yes?
Look into that man.
And be thorough about it.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu